{
    "id": "753f245306674d56914a4fd64bae0316",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… tired.",
            "description": "When feel is used to talk about reactions and opinions, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfb0d03e0f3e4575b7f1f6fc3c3da15a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………………. amazing woman.",
            "description": "In exclamations, we use such before an adjective + plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "a such",
                "such an",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a047d38a6464c15ae195e6ae1ea9a55"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………………….. kind of you.",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b8b19d90a91474a97641454308df2f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. this kind of treatment from him.",
            "description": "Before an indirect object, wait and hope are followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't expect",
                "didn't hope",
                "didn't wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a2ac5c9d4c04af3bff2b2f39e266056"
        },
        {
            "question": "It seemed like he was wearing someone …………………………… coat.",
            "description": "Else has a possessive form – else’s.",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "else's",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdae821839474fa5a62757de30fb6782"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. tired to walk.",
            "description": "Too is not used with much before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de85d1fd0b2f45f0b05c11eb79707b93"
        },
        {
            "question": "This book is an ……………………………… account of the freedom struggle.",
            "description": "Exhaustive means comprehensive or thorough.",
            "answers": [
                "exhausted",
                "exhausting",
                "exhaustive"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3aa4555d8b554af6bd647b5c98fb55e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have difficulty ……………………………. dates and numbers.",
            "description": "Difficulty is followed by (in) + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "remembering",
                "in remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "46768963b6f34f53bd69ac0947998658"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is something ……………………………..the bed.",
            "description": "We use under when something is covered by what is over it.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f26fe3297004ec6bc05f230b6b15c76"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like this house ………………………., it is too small.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "565823e47fbd4c2ca4a553fa2eec53b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t ………………………………… the car.",
            "description": "We make machines start.",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "begin"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f18a01644e9b40e8b653de9701b191b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "If my grandfather had been alive, we …………………………………… his 90th birthday in January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have celebrated",
                "would celebrate",
                "would have celebrated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6df7c44dacd24065aa588589739be9e6"
        }
    ]
}